{
    "id": "5bcc12bb0916405fb6b280a6d6cfb387",
    "title": "Conditional Clauses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you …………………  hard, you will get a first class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "study",
                "studied",
                "had studied"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If I …………………… the key, I will give it to you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "found",
                "had found"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If we …………………… now, we could be in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "start",
                "started",
                "had started"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If it ……………………, the match may be cancelled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rains",
                "rained",
                "had rained"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………… a millionaire, how would you spend your time?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "were",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If he ……………………… smoking, he might get well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stopped",
                "stops",
                "had stopped"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If he …………………  English, he could find a good job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speaks",
                "spoke",
                "had spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If he ………………………, he would have succeeded.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tries",
                "tried",
                "had tried"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………… that wasp alone, it might not have stung you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If I …………………, I could have married anybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wanted",
                "had wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}